
[
    {
    
    "mcq":[
    {
    "questionText": "Q: Which planet is the closest to the Sun?",
    "answersOptions": [
      { "answerText": "Venus", "isCorrect": false },
      {"answerText": "Mercury", "isCorrect": true },
      { "answerText": "Earth", "isCorrect": false },
      { "answerText": "Mars", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Q:Which data structure organizes items in a First-In, First-Out (FIFO) manner?",
    "answersOptions": [
      { "answerText": "Stack", "isCorrect": false },
      {"answerText": "Queue", "isCorrect": true },
      { "answerText": "Tree", "isCorrect": false },
      { "answerText": "Graph", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Q:Which of the following is primarily used for structuring web pages?",
    "answersOptions": [
      { "answerText": "Python", "isCorrect": false },
      {"answerText": "Java", "isCorrect": false },
      { "answerText": "HTML", "isCorrect": true },
      { "answerText": "C++", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Q: Which chemical symbol stands for Gold?",
    "answersOptions": [
      { "answerText": "Au", "isCorrect": true },
      {"answerText": "Gd", "isCorrect": false },
      { "answerText": "Ag", "isCorrect": false },
      { "answerText": "Pt", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Q: Which of these processes is not typically involved in refining petroleum",
    "answersOptions": [
      { "answerText": "Fractional distillation", "isCorrect": false },
      {"answerText": "Cracking", "isCorrect": false },
      { "answerText": "Polymerization", "isCorrect": false },
      { "answerText": "Filtration", "isCorrect": true }
    ]
  }



],
"integer":[
    {
      "questionText":"Q:What is the value of 12 + 28?",
      "answerText":40
    },
    {
        "questionText":"Q:How many states are there in the United States?",
        "answerText":50
      },
      {
        "questionText":"Q:In which year was the Declaration of Independence signed?",
        "answerText":1776
      },
      {
         "questionText":"Q:What is the value of pi rounded to the nearest intger?",
        "answerText":3
      },
      {
        "questionText":"If a car travels at 60 mph for 2 hours, how many miles does it travel?",
        "answerText":120
      }

]

}
  
]